NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE FILMING
OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
It's really him!
Oh my Allah, it's surely him!
While walking in darkness...
without my shadow...
I killed my enemies...
and lost my friends.
My ancestors' shrines were destroyed.
After I shouted for freedom...
I lost my voice.
I have so many troubles.
I am not only surrounded by ambushes...
but also betrayals.
My heart aches...
as well as my being.
The imminent draws near, Osman.
The persecution is about come to an end.
Time will give us a new resurrection.
As long as you do not fall asleep.
As long as you do not fall asleep, my son!
Kin of Oghuz only go through bad incidents
when they are asleep.
Wake up, my son!
Rise! My Son!
''Kin of Oghuz only go through bad
incidents when they are asleep.''
My mighty, grandfather!
Holy Yama!
The pain and torture...
I served to Osman and his family.
Are only for you.
Death is only for you.
All these plunders and booties are for
you.
From your iron and muddy castle...
Hear the voice of Balgay!
Accept this present from Balgay!
Ever since I started to serve Genghis
Khan...
All the blood I shed...
Gave pleasure to your mighty castle!
The tears of those I sacrificed...
had reached to Doymadım River...
then gave glory to our spirits.
As well as reputation.
Now...
I serve you...
Osman!
For Erluk Khan!
Rise, my son!
Osman.
What's wrong, brother?
I hope nothing is wrong, brother.
A dream within a dream.
A trick within a trick.
My Bey, we are ready.
With your permission, we can leave.
I don't want any mistakes.
We gave such a deposit to Balgay to claim
our Tent back...
that now it's time we take it back.
Now we will teach those Mongol dogs what
it means to lose.
Balgay will drown in his own dreams.
If Allah permits.
We will become the worst dreams of
Heathens.
We must howl like wolves and set the
biggest ambush ever for those tyrants.
We must be as sharp as Zulfiqar and bring
peace upon this land.
Let's go!
Oh, Allah!
May Allah help us!
May Allah be with us!
We are almost ready.
Do you want anything else, Balgay?
I only want the mighty Beys of Mongols...
to see who is holding the holy agenda of
almighty Genghis Khan...
And who the true monarch is...
so that they bow in front of Balgay!
Geyhatu will be so angry when he hears
the Beys bow to you...
and that you hold the holy agendas.
They will become your enemies, Balgay.
Those who become the enemies of Balgay
should look for strong allies, Cerkutay.
I am the new monarch.
And those are the commanders
of my army.
Soon, in Constantinople, our language will
be spoken!
Nothing besides this matters.
Kayıs are the first ones to beg.
A Hatun without a man is
like an infertile soil.
Imbecile Dündar.
Walk!
How is the situation in Söğüt, Erkut?
Balgay has left Söğüt.
They say he moved his Tent to
somewhere hidden.
No one can have their own Tents on
these soils except my father!
Those who attempt this shall die next to
their tents.
They bullied the merchants of
our Bazaar my Bey.
They took their goods and assaulted them.
What do they aim by that?
They want to bring food to Balgay.
Head Beys of Mongols are on their way.
And Balgay will have a feast tonight.
Those thieves will show us Balgay's
location.
Do you understand, my Konur?
As you wish, my Bey!
I will rip their lungs and present them to
you!
You should be all careful!
Let's go now!
Why is the Hatun of Kayıs...
bows in front of me.
Mighty Balgay!
I have some words to tell you.
Tell me already...
But be careful, you will understand the
death which comes from Balgay...
only when your spirit meets with sky.
I came here for my son.
He has left the Tent.
You are my only hope.
Why should I care...
about your son?
My son is with Osman at the moment.
He clashes next to Osman.
You say don't drink my son's blood...
don't drill his lungs...
don't feed the birds and wolves with his
head.
What do you offer in exchange?
Osman...
and...
Edebali.
So you came here with promises.
In exchange for what I desire...
you want to reunite with your son.
The person who doesn't think before
promising something...
must not cry...
when she fails to fulfill what she
promised.
You are a smart woman.
You exactly know who to obey.
My power stands with you.
Now, leave.
Then report me the information you
promised.
If you do something wrong...
I will separate Batur's flesh
from his bones.
Then, feed my dogs with him.
Don't you worry.
Zöhre will be loyal to you.
The number of dogs I control increases.
Give the word immediately.
Bring her husband here.
Dündar deserves a present now.
Where is your mother, my daughter?
She said she will leave to pick up medical
herbals.
Couldn't she find a better time?
Father, you know my mother.
She can't keep her mouth shut.
If she can't share her problems with us...
she will try to talk about them with
flowers.
Herbals are only her excuses.
What is it that problem she can't talk
about with us?
You have been wearing down my mother
lately, father.
Don't worry, my daughter.
Your mother always knew what she did.
She isn't anything like those herbals she
collects.
Don't say that.
You broke her heart so much.
I heard you asked for the presence of
Hazal Hatun and brother Bahadır.
How could you forget what happened
so quickly?
Dinner table of a Bey should be as wide
as his Tent, my daughter.
A person who knows how to act will not be
troubled with such matters.
You should finish your dinner, not be
overwhelmed with these.
Come on.
Do you think it is easy?
One of my brothers is on the road...
while there is no news from Batur brother.
May I come in, uncle?
You may come in, Gündüz.
You demanded my presence, uncle.
Come.
Sit.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Be my guest.
Thank you, uncle.
The situation of our Tent is
obvious, nephew.
Mongols...
destroyed everything along with
our people.
I want you to leave for Nicaea.
The Bazaar is very fertile there.
You need to sell everything we have
without any questions.
Uncle.
If that's what you want, I will go there.
Osman?
What's going to happen to Osman?
Osman is being punished by his
youthfulness right now.
He will learn from his lessons day by day.
Don't worry, my nephew.
I prepared such a great plan that...
in the end, everyone will get what they
want.
Also, I will hug him as soon as he comes
back...
and gain his heart again.
As you say, uncle.
Don't worry.
I will leave as soon as I can.
Tell the Tent guarding Alps to move into
forest.
They should defend this position in case
of a sneak attack.
Understood, our Bey!
My Bey, Bamsı Bey has arrived.
Let him come in.
What made you come all the way
to here, Bamsı Bey?
I didn't think you would know the road
to our Tent.
When I first came to these lands, there
were no ways at all.
Neither time nor the location is the same.
Bamsi Bey.
The youth started to riot against their
Beys.
I came here because of the exact problem.
I heard the wild winds started a breeze
between two high mountains.
I couldn't believe when I heard the
incident.
Now, tell me.
What happened?
Kill me right here, right now. Osman.
Or else I will find you.
Kill me!
Don't you ever dare to be on my path
again.
Eventually, those we praised proved
themselves unworthy...
and they wanted to go on their
own way, Bamsı Bey.
Do you hear what you are telling me right
now?
There are sometimes sad incidents like
this between comrades like us.
But, only for the sake of our path.
Osman has fallen both from my eyes and
my heart, Bamsı Bey.
You are two Valiants of Kayıs.
This is not how you are supposed to act.
You are brothers in arms!
If we are brothers in arms...
Why did he keep the agendas as a secret?
Ertuğrul Bey also had secrets.
But we weren't offended at all.
Dündar...
sent him to exile after he learned about
it.
Why didn't you say anything back then?
Dündar is our Bey.
We can't question his orders.
Yeah, Dündar Bey.
This is the Tent he rules.
This is the throne.
Aren't we as important as
our Bey Dündar, Bamsı Bey?
A Bey doesn't hesitate when he gives the
commands!
A Bey always knows his place when he
confronts a mistake!
A Bey always tries to come up with
solutions instead of running away!
This spear doesn't fit its sack, Bamsı
Bey.
From now on, Osman is my enemy.
Nothing else.
Don't stand between us so that no blood
will be spilled onto you.
You are newbie Valiant.
Right now...
you are the Bey of the Tent your father
left you.
But there is one thing...
they either didn't teach you well...
or you didn't understand it well enough.
Samsa.
I...
am the right hand of Ertuğrul Ghazi...
mighty Bamsı Beyrek.
I whet my sword with blood...
and live side by side with my fate.
As you elder, I give preaches to you.
But you try to darken upon us.
If you continue with this stubbornness...
you will be alone more than ever.
Wolves howl at our naiveness...
while the birds make fun of them.
Loneliness is my destiny, Bamsı Bey.
You spent so much effort on us...
but this has nothing to do with you.
If you disagree, the door is there.
All the effort I spent you...
all the effort I spent...
I feel sad for them.
You...
have become presumptuous.
You forgot about our moral laws.
Evil has set a tent inside your spirit.
Now...
you'll either destroy his tent and get rid
of the Devil...
or nobody can save you from me.
I'll give you some time to think...
If I see that Devil in your spirit
again...
I will destroy this Tent upon you.
I will destroy this Tent upon you, Samsa.
Please stop.
Don't do it.
Leave us alone.
Go there!
I beg you, please stop.
You took everything I have.
Enough already.
At least give my horses back.
Balgay is waiting for you, Dündar Bey.
Do you know what he demands from me?
Balgay doesn't demand, he takes,
Dündar Bey.
He just takes.
Stop! Stop!
Hang their bodies to the side of the road.
Those who pass by shall see them.
So that this fear of the Mongols perishes.
They should see that Osman and his Alps
have rekindled the fire of resurrection.
Let's go. We have a long night ahead.
In the name of Kayı Tent, I've come to
inform you that...
... we've accepted your
leadership, Balgay.
Blessed commander, almighty Balgay.
Balgay likes you.
You've started to come to reason, Dündar.
And you exiled Osman.
From now on, those who might hurt our
loyalty to you can't populate Kayı Tent.
More loyal you are to Balgay,
more graceful he will be.
Your brother Ertuğrul was generous and
made you...
... the alternate Bey of the Kayı Tent.
Now I will be like a father to you.
Stand up.
From now on you are, not the alternate,
but the noble Bey of the Kayı Tent.
These golds are my gift to you.
Spend them, or hand them out as you wish.
How could that be? Kayı Tent's throne is
my brother's.
Beys won't accept this.
Don't worry, Dündar.
Easy there, Dündar.
Balgay is very generous. I also grant you
the Bannerlordship which all Beys follow.
Now go and fly this mighty symbol
in the Kayı Tent.
So that everyone knows
the Mongols' power...
... who swear on ruling every place
where the sun rises and sets.
Why me, Balgay?
Is there and other Bey
as brave as you, Dündar Bey?
Kayı Tent will always be grateful for you.
No need for empty words. I have
other guests. You may leave.
Bring me the laws and the guardian dagger.
Do you see what I see, my Bey?
I wish I was blind, Konur.
He offers his flesh to the dog
who attacked our Tent.
He begged Balgay so much that
his tongue wrinkled.
He kneeled so much that
his knees started to decay.
He rides his horse as if he won a victory.
What do you think he's doing in that
dog's Tent, my Bey?
My father's throne was the only thing
he didn't sell.
My Bey, do you think he's bold
enough to do this?
Move!
Our ancestor Genghis...
... descends from the blue wolf who lives
in the Burkhan Khaldun mountains.
I'll paint my face just blue.
I'll carry this dagger which is
a reminiscence from...
... our ancestor Genghis with honour
Don't turn your face away, Selcan Hatun.
Don't increase my troubles.
If you had yourself together, you'd not
have such big troubles.
If I made mistakes, it's because
I was scared.
My fears have come true. My valiant son
went away.
Come with me, Selcan Hatun.
I have things to tell you.
Important things.
I don't have much time.
Say whatever you want to say.
A child causes sorrow a thousand times
more to the mother.
You'll understand this.
- Take this fardel.
- What is this?
To my Batur.
I don't know where he is.
You're in touch with Osman.
You'll definitely hear
something about him.
They shall give it to my Batur.
Clean clothes for him.
- Zöhre!
- Don't, Selcan Hatun!
I know what you are going to say.
But your words don't heal my wounds.
Dündar Bey disowned Batur.
Worse, he told Bahadır to bring
his mother with him.
What are you talking about, Zöhre?
Are Bahadır and his mother coming here?
- We're doomed.
- I'm begging you, Selcan Hatun.
Make this fardel reach my Batur.
About Osman...
I understand. I understand him and
why Batur went with him.
I agree with him.
If you hear something about Osman.
Tell me.
Knowing that they are doing okay
is enough.
I hope Osman doesn't do
something crazy, brother.
How can you call someone who's not crazy
a Bey, brother?
Didn't we stay quiet in the meeting so he
could tear his heart out?
Those who don't suffer can't be Beys.
He'll suffer greatly so that
he can be the hope...
... of these people in the
future, brother.
Thank you, you're right, Bamsı brother.
My heart will be torn apart if something
bad happens to Osman.
Bamsı! Brother!
Do you see what I'm seeing?
Abdurrahman brother! These eyes witnessed
such betrayals...
... but they never saw
something like this.
I never saw or heard something like this.
What are we going to do now?
Long live Dündar Bey!
Kayı's valiant Beys, valiant Alps,
and community.
I'm flying another flag beside
the blessed flag of Kayı...
... worthy of my ancestor Oghuz, my father
Süleyman Şah
I wanted you to know and be proud.
I did another great thing for these lands
my brother Ertuğrul Bey conquered.
I was blessed with, with my Allah's
permission, the Bannerlordship.
Because of this, Kayıs are
full of hope once again!
Long live Dündar Bey!
With me being the Bannerlord,
in these lands or in our Tent...
... we've come to the end of living
without leaders.
We'll work more, we'll strive more!
You traitor! I hope Osman comes here
and destroys your fake magnificence!
Selcan Hatun wait! Not now. Not now.
As the Kayıs Bey and
the Bannerlord of these lands...
... I'm waiting for my Tent's
Beys in my tent.
Just like me, their duties
and responsibilities also increased.
May Allah help you all.
- Long live Dündar Bey!
Genghis Khan's laws are in Balgay's tent.
My Bey! This won't be easy.
Balgay invited over a great Mongol
commander for tonight.
He wants to be more powerful. He wants to
advance in the Mongol khanate.
We'll crush his spirit.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Let's go.
Now I'm both the Bey of Kayı Tent
and the Bannerlord.
Dark days are gone.
Duty came with its blessings.
Saltuk!
We didn't say anything so you could
get the Tent together!
But does being Mongols' friend mean?
I made these decisions for Kayı's safety.
Brothers! The Mongols
are way stronger than us!
We're not strong enough to deal with them.
Don't you still understand?
I want to have good senses
and protect our Tent from trouble.
Why did you take the gold then?
Does freedom have a price?
I've been assisting this Tent for years.
I've never seen such a thing!
In Kayı, Beys choose the Bey.
Who chose you?
Who put you in that throne, Dündar Bey?
What was I supposed to do?
Cause another slaughter?
Kayı's fortune was gained with blood!
I wish they broke my neck so
I couldn't see you kneel, Dündar Bey!
What was he supposed to do? Refuse the
duties and refuse to kneel?
Let the Mongols decide the Tent's fate?
We saw those who refused. Mr Blacksmith.
They destroyed Kayı's dignity.
They became Balgay's cattle.
Şahin Bey! Revolting and
becoming cattle...
... is better than kneeling and
being their dog!
Enough! Watch your words,
Abdurrahman Gazi!
No, Dündar Bey! No!
Abdurrahman Gazi is right!
History of a battle also
includes the defeat.
But it doesn't include the dishonour
that comes from taking your enemy's gold.
Watch your words, Bamsı Beyrek!
Otherwise you won't be a Bey or an Alp!
Dündar Bey! My hairs turned grey when
my son became a martyr!
If we were going to kneel like this, why
did we let so many of us die?
Dündar Bey! Enemy's oily foods have
seduced you out of your faith.
But know this.
Every cloud has a silver lining.
These reactions are inevitable, my Beys.
We don't doubt the road we're
headed towards.
Saltuk! Hand the remaining gold out to
other Beys.
Open!
Approach, Selcan Hatun.
Do you want me to crawl or walk,
Dündar Bey?
Because, you've been a dog of Mongols.
Your traditions may have changed.
Watch your mouth, Selcan Hatun!
I watch my mouth according to
my traditions, Dündar Bey.
Hatun, man things, politics, are beyond
your ken.
Mind your own business, let me not
break your heart.
Oh hey, look at Sheik Süleyman Shah's
son Dündar Bey.
Look what this Bey says. He was supposed
to honor Kayı Tribe.
What my Osman should do now?
You've been a slave for Mongols.
Who can stop Osman now?
From now on...
From now on, whatever I say is law.
Osman is the one who brought us here.
Should I have let Mongols
destroy our tribe?
You are talking about the glory of Kayı.
I didn't pay attention to that, I had to
protect us.
Kayı is the banner lord of this country
now.
Don't talk any more.
Or you'll be exiled.
Pull yourself together.
Enough, Dündar Bey.
Stop.
You're arguing with everyone.
First Osman, then Batur, now Selcan Hatun.
This Hatun is traditional. She cares about
the tribe. What do you mean by exile?
My Batur followed Osman's path.
If Selcan Hatun goes, I and my daughter
will go with her, too.
This is a blessed day.
This is a great, blessed day, Kongar!
What do you want from us, Balgay?
Why are you in hurry to talk with us?
The souls' power has been my armor.
Cengiz Han's mouth has become mine,
so has his sword.
The power in my blood comes from Cengiz
Han's laws.
You should know that.
Bring the chest!
My Batur Bey...
Be ready.
We will not go without a kill for sure,
my Konur.
Who are you?
I asked who you are!
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman.
My Bey, they are coming to take the chest.
My Bey, they are waiting for the chest.
They'd better wait.
Be ready for the battle.
Come on.
Cengiz Han's power is with me.
Geyhatun's brave Commanders.
The laws that carry Cengiz Han's soul...
are in Balgay's blessed hand.
May the souls witness.
May they be my friend.
Today, we obey the laws' power.
Do you hear what you are saying, Balgay?
This power can only belong to
Cengiz Han's grandchildren.
Not in your hand!
Power is with me, Commander Taloy.
Power...
is with Balgay.
If Balgay is right, he will want us to
obey, or he'll kill us.
The chest is empty, Balgay.
Betrayal.
Are you playing with us?
Balgay! What do you think you are doing?
You won't go anywhere until we find
Cengiz Han's laws.
Search everywhere!
Close the entrances and exits.
We are going.
Kneel!
Search everywhere!
Come on, Alps!
There are dead Alps in the
back of the tribe. They ran from there.
Kungar is following them.
This must be Osman.
Search everywhere, Cerkutay!
I swear on my ancestor Cengiz's soul...
I will tear Osman's flesh apart his bones.
I will drink his blood and prepare a
feast from his flesh!
I know you are ambitious.
You loved the power.
But I didn't expect this.
One should be prepared for what he
doesn't expect, Hatun.
You bothered me so much.
Now, you wonder what will
happen to you and you are worried.
Am I your new enemy?
No, you have gone mad.
Didn't you say that "In Kayı, everyone
has power..."
but only you have both power and wisdom."
Ha?
Let this tribe benefit from my wisdom.
You couldn't be a father to your son.
Are you talking about being a Bey?
I'd laugh, Dündar Bey.
You've been talking about Beylik (Beyship)
and power for years.
Here is the Bey, here is the power!
If you don't like, the door is open.
I've had enough!
Lucky you.
You have protected the entrustment.
You have deflated the enemy.
Thank my Allah, my Sheik.
This life, this world, this body,
this greenery
all are entrusted to humans.
So, a human must be Al-Emin (trustworthy)
He must protect the entrustments.
How can we do it, my Sheik?
By being a human.
Aren't we humans already?
Physically, yes.
What about mentally?
What about spiritually?
What about in your heart?
We came to this world as humans.
Are we going to go to the hereafter
as humans, Osman Bey?
Just like there is a way to go
somewhere...
Just like science has its own way...
There is a way to go to hereafter
as a human, for sure.
What is that way, my Sheik?
Protecting the entrustment, son.
Firstly, we will clear our hearts.
Because, a sacred hadith says...
" I couldn't take place in the whole world
but, I could take place in a Muslim heart.
We will be wise, son.
We are not going to be interested in
bubbling.
We are always going to think of
good deeds.
We will protect the world, and make the
universe prosperous.
While doing something, we are going to
calculate everything, and not hurt anyone.
We are not going to deform the world.
We are not going to hurt the animals.
We are not going to turn nature into
a human trash.
We are an Al-Emin (trustworthy) Prophet's
community.
We have to be Al-Emin (trustworthy) in
every place we take.
In family, in government works,
in commerce, in agriculture.
We are not going to lose
this characteristic.
Because, if we can't our Allah's
entrustment...
we will be disgraced.
The ones who protect the entrustment
will decide the fate of the future.
Al-Emins ( Trustworthy ones) will
resurrect this state.
Allah is with Al-Emins
(Trustworthy ones).
Stop!
I said stop! What are you doing?
Give it to me!
What do you think you are doing, heh?
Won't you be ashamed against Ertuğrul Bey?
Are you ignoring the tradition of Kayı?
It's Dündar Bey's order, Selcan Hatun.
Let it be.
Damn your manhood.
Damn your courage.
Saltuğ. Didn't your father grow up with
my Sheik Süleyman?
Ha?
What about you?
Didn't your father become a martyr while
fighting for Ertuğrul Bey?
No! I will not let you loot my Ertuğrul
Bey's tent!
Don't, Selcan Hatun.
Talk to the Bey.
I can't believe this.
There is no Bey to hear me out.
I wish I was blind and not see this.
Protect us, my Allah.
Go to Cerkutay immediately. Selcan Hatun
is out of the tribe.
Where she is going is obvious.
My Bala...
I want to come with you.
I don't want you to go alone.
Don't worry, it won't take long.
I will see Selcan Hatun, talk a bit.
Selcan Hatun knows Osman the best,
Gonca Hatun.
I want to freshen up.
She will show me the way.
You still don't look at my face.
I was mistaken about you, Osman Bey.
I don't want to push you.
I will tell the truth again, maybe
you couldn't understand me.
My accompany needs to...
know where to be deaf, and where to be
a bow.
However, if you suspect, it's hard
of course.
I am not the one who suspects, it's you,
Osman Bey.
Obviously, we are getting nowhere.
I can't talk with someone who can't
hear what she is saying.
I brought the Nökers who were responsible
of the guards.
While my ancestor Cengiz's blessed
entrustment were being stolen...
didn't those ears hear anything?
The ear, which doesn't hear the enemy,
is useless!
Eyes, which doesn't see the enemy...
Useless eyes!
The Nöker who doesn't have the Mongol
nobility...
will be blind, will be deaf!
Burn them.
May the wolves and birds not be poisoned
with their useless flesh.
Did they manage to escape?
Wherever he goes, we will
find Osman, Balgay.
I don't need fancy words.
I want blood!
Like a flood, I want blood, Cerkutay!
Commander Balgay, the other Kayı tribe's
Bey Samsa...
he disagreed with Osman.
Our man in the tribe said.
An arrow to hunt an eagle...
is made of eagle's feathers.
Kongar, sacrifice a man of yours.
Send him to Samsa's tribe.
- And bring him to you?
- He will not come.
Now, what we need is Samsa's courage.
The man you send should play with
his pride so that...
Samsa kills him.
When he killed a couple of Mongols..
Freedom lover Kayıs will be gathered
around him.
At that exact time, with Osman's
ambition...
Samsa's courage will fight.
And we won't tire ourselves.
Put it properly, Alps!
My Father.
I will carry your entrustment with honor.
Shepherd, shepherd, if you die, who will
take care of these goats, shepherd?
Don't think I am a quiet sheep.
I swear on my father Süleyman Shah.
I will pay you off for what you've done,
Balgay.
I will.
Ignoble Balgay must have gone mad when
he found out that he lost the chest.
Balgay is the enemy we know, brother.
What about the factious' in us?
A community can't get rid of the enemies...
as long as they don't take care of the
factious'.
If someone becomes a factious...
he must be killed.
We will take care of them one by one.
We will tear their lungs apart!
Sons!
What's the problem, Bamsi Bey?
Dündar became flag officer of...
...Balgay, Osman.
What are you saying, Bamsi Bey!
Balgay declared him as a flag officer
in exchange for his obedience.
As a first duty, he displayed a flag of...
...flag officer near to our honourable
flag.
Father!
You shouldn't have done this.
Even Alisar wouldn't do such a thing.
Either freedom...
...or death.
Those who rebel control the chair...
...not those who obey.
Don't fall into error, guys.
Firstly, We'll solve these affairs.
Then we'll fall down the Tent.
We'll tear off that flag officer flag.
Move!
You go!
I'll come.
Come here.
Ya Allah.
Salvador.
Freak!
Don't struggle.
Leave him to me.
Leave.
Walk up!
I didn't betray.
Eshedu en la ilahe ilallah...
...ve eshedu ennemu muhammeden
abduhu ve resulu.
Liar factious.
You can't.
You can't go anywhere
this time.
You can't again.
Bamsi Bey.
Don't do it.
Listen to me, Bamsi Bey.
You leave him for me, Bamsi Bey.
Let Sıddık go!
Dont do it, my Bey.
I'm not gonna say it again.
Arghhh!
He is not Sıddık.
He is Salvador.
Salvador.
Are you okay?
Yes, Osman Bey.
They know nothing about it.
Sorry.
No problem, Osman Bey.
Is there any news?
Everything is going as planned
Sofia will request Balgay to trap you.
Osman.
Is he really Sıddık?
I promised something to you, Bamsi Bey.
I will be loyal to my promise
until I am dead.
If they play with us...
...we'll, too.
As long as we continue to struggle.
I see the reflection of Ertugrul Bey
through your eyes.
He is such a man that...
...he sees back of the mountains.
...he lights a fire behind the fog.
Well done, brave man!
Well done.
Masha Allah (praise be), my Bey.
Long live with your intelligence.
Well done.
Mashallah.
Now, I will go to give the entrustment
Be ready when I come.
We will fall down the Tent.
Let's do it, Osman.
You couldn't guess the right time, woman.
While Balgay is blood-thirsty...
...you appear before him.
In contrast, there couldn't
be better time to meet than now...
...great commander Balgay.
I heard that...
...Osman took what he had given.
From where did you hear?
You came from away.
We've been here for 1000 years.
Did you eventually
learn why I hate Osman that much?
He is a rabid dog.
He is a troubler.
If you listen to me...
...you'll have the road
which goes to hunting.
How?
Osman has someone who he trusts so much.
And he serves to me.
You're sneaky as a marten.
and smart as a fox.
What do you want in return?
You will understand, Balgay.
We'll speak calmly.
By the name of 99 names of great Allah...
...who fills our heart with faith and
makes whatever he wants happen.
The nobles of my Tent.
Ghazi Beys.
The Kayı fell from grace...
...because of Dundar's improper
behaviours.
While he took the chair of Ertugrul
Bey thanks to Mongol,
he brought flag of Mongol and planted
it to the Kayı Oba.
From now on, we have hope.
Soon...
...mongols will bother our Tent.
We are few in number, my Bey.
We can't resist.
There must be a miracle to defeat them.
Do we need to wait for swift birds to battle
with tyrants who occupy Muslim homelands.
Those swift birds will throw stones at us
first if we don't rebel.
Don't we have a time...
...of death after all?
Now that death comes just 1 time,
I am asking you...
...why shouldn't it come for	martyrdom?
I hope nothing's wrong, inshallah.
My bey.
Mongols...
If I came here for war...
...I wouldn't come like that.
My visiting is friendly.
We don't have any friendship with the
tyranny.
Our rage is with those who don't obey us.
What've we done to your Tent?
Tell me why you came here.
Commander Balgay wants you in his marquee
in Kartalkaynı.
What does he want from me?
Balgay doesn't request, he just takes.
If you come, it will be beneficial to
the Tent.
What if I don't?
This time you can't rescue just
by being pack animal, Samsa.
Balgay will be your butcher.
We'll show around your head in
all Oba as a deterrent.
Announce it to all the Tents...
...Samsa Bey started the fire of freedom.
All right, my Bey!
Betrayal.
Betrayal!
I've done my duty unconditionally.
Bey father.
I'm proud of you always.
But, you honoured me this time.
I can do everything for you, Bey father.
May your banner lordship and Kayı Beyship
be everlasting
May Allah don't make you away from us.
Osman
He'll learn what you've done
sooner or later.
I know.
He'll pursue you.
I'll be cautious this time.
The pain of the dagger that
he stabbed to my chest has relieved.
But...
It's rage is still alive
inside my body.
May Allah protect us.
My son.
My Batur.
Mother.
My son.
I brought your son to you.
Don't mess with my decisions again.
You are the hope of the Kayı, Dundar Bey.
If I make you sad because of my
mother instincts...
...forgive me.
May your banner lordship be everlasting.
Is there any problem, my Bey?
Betrayal.
Betrayal!
What did Batur say, Aykut?
He said I would go to
hunting and went out, my Bey.
We've everything in here. Why would
he go to hunting in this situation?
Old habits die hard.
To where, my Bey?
To take the life of Batur.
Do you think it can continue like that,
Selcan Hatun?
I say I can do everything for you.
He says It's secret.
Is there a secret to loving heart?
Look. You are silent.
There is nothing to say.
Now that Osman doesn't trust me...
...he doesn't need my companionship
as well.
He said that already.
We came to a dead end.
You came to a dead end, huh?
I know him.
It seems he is angry with you.
I thought he loved me so much.
But now I understand that
he doesn't love me anymore.
Look at me.
Being one and bear others and
bearing each other are not the same thing.
You'll learn it later.
Burden of love is the same
for both sides.
It's all about having a heart that can
bear this burden.
My Osman surely loves you.
But he has the blood
of Oguz in his vessels.
His grandfather and father
fell in love, too.
But they said first Tent and traditions
came.
Their wives were the same.
Halime mother didn't ask so many things
to Suleyman.
Without knowing the reason, Halime Sultan
said "okay" to Ertugrul Bey nearly always.
Being wife means being silent and...
...accepting some things.
Otherwise, this love will come to an end.
So you're saying that you've
done something wrong.
You're saying that you broke
Osman's heart in vain.
I'm saying that as long as there
is not treachery in love...
...there isn't dead end.
Maybe Osman is broken.
But if you want to please him...
...he is already your love.
I thought he wouldn't
believe and trust me.
His passion makes me so happy.
But if he doesn't accept me,
I will fall down.
Look at me, my daughter.
Hold on to this love tightly.
Osman won't allow you to fall down
as long as he doesn't.
Don't worry.
Take this to Batur.
His mother sent it.
It's mother's love, my daughter.
Mother worries about her son.
Make it happen.
All the best!
Thanks, Selcan Hatun.
Be ready
We'll pursue the girl.
She'll take us to Osman.
Come on!
Come on.
May Allah protect us.
Our road will divide in here.
Take whoever follows us away.
Come on!
Catch her.
Come.
You're all gathered just because of
the fear of one woman.
Come then!
Didn't I told you...
...that you wouldn't...
...damage her?
We kept good burden
this winter, my Bey.
The society is being happy about that as
spring comes.
We've deserved it, Saltuk Alp.
We've faced so many difficulties.
Argh!
Batur!
I told you that there's no excuse...
...for villainy and no compensation
for treachery, Batur.
You didn't listen to me.
I trusted you.
I said you "My brother."
What did you do?
You fooled me.
You sold the dignity
of your father and Kayı at once.
As your father betrayed Ertugrul
Bey and broke the laws...
...you broke me, Batur!
You will pay the price!
Osman!
Batur!
Brother!
Don't do it, brother!
Please!
Osman!
Let me go!
Bastards!
Wait.
Osman!
Batur!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com